ERMEK BARMASHEV

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 631 4848

BARMASHEV48@GMAIL.COM

WWW.ERMEKCODES.COM

GITHUB.COM/BARMASHEV

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- Vanilla JavaScript, JQuery, React
- Working with RESTful APIs, Firebase
- Responsive Design
- Web accessibility
- Version control and collaboration using Git and GitHub

PROFILE

I am a front end developer with experience in customer service and sales/marketing who is committed to making web more accessible. I love writing clean code and learning new technologies as well as collaborating with team members on the projects.

EXPERIENCE

CASHIER

SUMMERHILL MARKET | FEB 2020 - OCT 2020

- Promptly scanned items and collected payments,
- Using scanning devices, answering to customer inquiries in a an efficient, friendly manner
- Successfully trained new cashiers

MARKET STRATEGY AND PLANNING INTERN

PROCTER & GAMBLE KAZAKHSTAN | FEB 2019 - MAY 2019

- Managed Oral Care category in Kazakhstan
- Successfully launched a line of electric oral care toothbrushes
- Presented market overview to the Regional Director
- Managed distribution in key supermarket chains

EDUCATION

IMMERSIVE WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | 2020 - 2021 TORONTO, CANADA

BACHELOR OF INTERNATIONAL LAW

AL-FARABI KAZAKH NATIONAL UNIVERSITY | 2012 - 2016 ALMATY, KAZAKHSTAN

FEATURED PROJECTS

LIKELY MATCH

BASED ON A USER INPUT GENERATES A PLAYLIST OF SIMILAR SONGS AND STORES IT IN FIREBASE DATABASE LIVE GITHUB REPO

BLACK JACK

A GAME OF BLACK JACK THAT DEALS CARDS TO THE PLAYER AND A DEALER, COUNTS THE CARDS AND DISPLAYS THE WINNER

LIVE GITHUB REPO